Join Barbie as Elina in an all-new Fairytopia adventure!
Barbie Fairytopia: Magic of the Rainbow is a animation,
family, fantasy film directed by William Lau.
Elina goes to a fairy school to learn dancing and fairy magic.
The spring of the fairy land is soon threatened by evil Laverna who intends to
prevent fairies from performing the annual vital rainbow dance.
Elina must stop quarreling with her fellow students and
unite them to save the first bud of the spring.
Elina (voice), played by Kelly Sheridan.
Bibble / Fungus #1 & #2 (voice), played by Lee Tockar.
Laverna (voice), played by Kathleen Barr.
Fungus Maximus (voice), played by Christopher Gaze.
Dandelion / Topaz (voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Azura / Pixie #1 (voice), played by Venus Terzo.
Barbie Fairytopia: Magic of the Rainbow, also known as Barbie: Magic of the Rainbow is a 2007 animated fantasy film
directed by William Lau and written by Elise Allen that released direct-to-video on March 17, 2007.
It was distributed internationally through Universal Pictures Video.
It is the tenth installment in the Barbie film series and the
third film in the Barbie: Fairytopia trilogy.
The film follows Elina, who is chosen to attend fairy school at the
Crystal Palace as an apprentice of the Guardian fairy Azura.
Elina and the six other apprentices will prepare for the annual spring ritual, the
"Flight of Spring", that produces the first rainbow of the season.
The antagonist of the series, Laverna, is planning to stop the
rite and plunge Fairytopia into ten years of winter.
Elina must work together with the apprentices to
defeat Laverna and save Fairytopia.
The film explores themes of magic, fairy, based on
toy, female protagonist, magic land.
The tone is emotional.